I love travelling in the country, but I don't like losing my way.
I went on an excursion recently, but my trip took me longer than I expected.
'I'm going to Woodford Green,' I said to the conductor as I got on the bus, 'but I don't know where it is.'
'I'll tell you where to get off.'
answered the conductor.
I sat in the front of the bus to get a good view of the countryside.
After some time, the bus stopped.
Looking round, I realized with a shock that I was the only passenger left on the bus.
'You'll have to get off here,' the conductor said.
'This is as far as we go.'
'Is this Woodford Green?'
I asked.
'Oh dear,' said the conductor suddenly.
'I forgot to put you off.'
'It doesn't matter,' I said.
'I'll get off here.'
'We're going back now,' said the conductor.
'Well, in that case, I prefer to stay on the bus,' I answered.